...
Get out.
Come on.
How you doing?
Handpicked by our people in Atlanta.
Fresh off the boat.
Let's take a look.
(PANTING)
Oh.
Nice.
Top-of-the-line.
This is exactly
what we were looking for.
Wow.
Nice work. You got it, boss.
Fence, Dolan. Get 'em into the van.
Move it.
Go, go.
Please. Let me go.
You're gonna be okay. I promise.
Trust me. Come on.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
- What do we got?
- Vic is Nia Fox.
BAEZ: Looks like her
husband tuned her up.
Neighbor called it in.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Mind if we have a word?
Nia, I'm Detective Reagan,
this is my partner Detective Baez.
How you doing?
This isn't necessary.
I'm-I'm... I'm okay.
You don't look okay.
Your husband do this to you?
We had an argument.
Looks more like a fight.
A loud enough fight
that your neighbors called 911.
James lost his temper.
Okay? He's-he's really a good guy.
He ever done this to you before?
He's... T-There's just
a lot of pressure at work.
Where's your husband now?
NIA: He's at work.
But I'm not gonna press charges.
Well, we still need to speak to him.
(EXHALES)
DANNY: James Fox.
- Yes?
- Detectives Reagan and Baez.
You got a second to talk?
What's this about?
We went by your house.